Happy New Year!
Oh? Dad went off to train with Uncle.
Training? I haven't heard anything about that.
It's just a form of training where you get drunk anyway.
Come on, let's eat!
Wow,
Wow, all of this was handmade by my big sister Kasumi.
Black Beans Peeled Kito Small Beans Closed in Kombu - What an amazing way to make it. Oh, these are shrimp and
Crayfish.
Tofu-sensei brought it. It's nothing special, but please accept it for the New Year.
I guess you just gave me the wrong thing anyway. I've removed the mud and seasoned it, so it's delicious. Besides, gravel crabs are kind of fitting for New Year's, aren't they?
What's so special about crayfish for New Year's?
It's red, it's a shellfish, and the double peace sign gives it a celebratory feel.
Please. Enjoy. I'll enjoy having this
I will
Yeah. Yeah.
Herring roe is delicious.
Crispy quiton is also delicious.
Hey sis, I got a New Year's card.
Yeah.
Yes.
Ah, it's from Ruga-kun.
Ruga? Yes. let's see. Yeah
Quantity? Yes. let's see. Yeah
Give it back. Happy new year
I'm currently undergoing mountain training in Aomori. It's warmer here than I expected, and the sea is absolutely beautiful.
Next time we meet, I'll bring you some Chinsuko sweets as a souvenir, so please look forward to it.
I think it might be Okinawa.
Clearly won't be back anytime soon.
Yeah. Oh yeah, I remembered that Kuno had given me a New Year's card to give to Ranma-kun.
Let's see
Let's see.
The woman with pigtails and a strong belief in the river. I hereby swear that this year too, I will give it my all to date a woman who loves to drink. That's crazy
He's the same this year too
I was supposed to have a message from my dad about his New Year's money.
New Year's money? You should have told me sooner.
The Tendou Cup New Year's Lucky Draw will now begin.
I hid four small envelopes somewhere in this house, and the contents of each are 20,000 yen.
It's fine if one person takes one, but it's also fine if no one gets one.
My first test of luck this year. He wishes you all good luck.
Dad, I'm not a kid anymore, so there's no way I'd take something like this so seriously.
He says, but then why is he stretching his Achilles tendon?
Your skirt is flipped up.
Huh? Oh, Nabiki-neechan is ahead. Come on,
Ranma-kun, you'd better hurry
or those two will snatch them up.
Huh? Oh, right.
I don't think they have it at the dojo.
If that's the case, maybe the girl who's been doing the nabbings could look for someone else.
Dad was doing something at home yesterday without even watching TV. He must have been hiding the lost ball.
It's definitely here.
Where?
Found it. Thank you very much
How much is in there?
Um,
3000 yen
Okay. Huh? Nabiki-neechan is gone.
We don't need three Soseki.
The only person I want to meet is Yukichi. Dad was secretly
eating some of the food yesterday, so the kitchen is suspicious.
What are you doing, big sister? I'm making curry
Ose is good, but curry is good too.
Big sister is really great, isn't she?
Oh, there's a small envelope inside the curry box.
Hmm,
Hmm, this feels like a 500 yen coin.
Something seems suspicious about the bathroom.
Ranma.
Wow, I found a small envelope for money behind the landlord's house.
Oh, it's a cat. Meow.
I received my New Year's money.
That's not fair.
This world is a dog-eat-dog world. I wonder how much it is?
5000 yen.
Dad was cleaning the pond yesterday, so it must be here.
Wait, Ranma.
Oh, it's a cat. Meow meow.
That hand is like a grilled tuna.
That money is mine.
Ranma
Ranma, would you trade that money envelope for my rice?
No. Stay here. 10,000 yen. Huh?
500 yen. So, what does that mean?
Everyone's going to their first shrine visit of the year soon, so let's get dressed for the sunny weather. Hey, hey. Ranma is all wet. You'll catch a cold.
In the end, my older sister found a money envelope containing
11,500 yen
A victory achieved through selflessness. It doesn't really matter,
But why am I wearing a kimono too? We're all going to the shrine for our first visit of the year, and you look cute
I'm not kidding. How can anyone walk around in something this tight?
Yes. I'll give you my New Year's money.
Oh, really?
Let's all wear our traditional Japanese clothing and go to the shrine for our first visit of the year.
Oh, I did it. Yukichi, I missed you. Huh?
500 yen?
I put 11,000 yen towards home repairs. You guys are going to cause a lot of trouble again this year.
That's definitely not enough, though.
Sorry.